half4you.net 2016-11-13

# Privacy policy - Half4yoU

Privacy policy  
This privacy policy ("Policy") describes how we collect, protect and use the personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you ("User", "you" or "your") provide on the [https://www.half4you.net](https://www.half4you.net/) website and any of its products or services (collectively, "Website" or "Services"). It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. This Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage.  
Collection of personal information  
We receive and store any information you knowingly provide to us when you create an account, publish content, fill any online forms on the Website. When required this information may include your email address, or other Personal Information. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of some of the Website's features.  
Collection of non-personal information  
When you visit the Website our servers automatically record information that your browser sends. This data may include information such as your computer's IP address, browser type and version, operating system type and version, language preferences or the webpage you were visiting before you came to our Website, pages of our Website that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our Website, access times and dates, and other statistics.  
Managing personal information  
You are able to access, add to, update and delete certain Personal Information about you. The information you can view, update, and delete may change as the Website or Services change. When you update information, however, we may maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you Services. Some information may remain in our private records after your deletion of such information from your account. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. We may use any aggregated data derived from or incorporating your Personal Information after you update or delete it, but not in a manner that would identify you personally.  
Use of collected information  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used to improve our website; improve customer service and respond to queries and emails of our customers; run and operate our Website and Services. Non-personal information collected is used only to identify potential cases of abuse and establish statistical information regarding Website traffic and usage. This statistical information is not otherwise aggregated in such a way that would identify any particular user of the system.  
Children  
We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personal information through our Website or Service. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children's Internet usage and to help enforce this Policy by instructing their children never to provide personal information through our Website or Service without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided personal information to us through our Website or Service, please contact us.  
Newsletters  
We offer electronic newsletters to which you may voluntarily subscribe at any time. You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or by contacting us. However you will continue to receive essential transactional emails.  
Links to other websites  
Our Website contains links to other websites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites or third parties. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that may collect personal information.  
Information security  
We secure information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. We maintain reasonable administrative, technical, and physical safeguards in an effort to protect against unauthorized access, use, modification, and disclosure of personal information in its control and custody. However, no data transmission over the Internet or wireless network can be guaranteed. Therefore, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that (i) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; (ii) the security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and our Website cannot be guaranteed; and (iii) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party, despite best efforts.  
Legal disclosure  
We will disclose any information we collect, use or receive if required or permitted by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process, and when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.  
Changes and amendments  
We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy relating to the Website or Services at any time, effective upon posting of an updated version of this privacy policy on the Website. When we do we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. Continued use of the Website after any such changes shall constitute your consent to such changes. Policy was created with WebsitePolicies.com  
Acceptance of this policy  
You acknowledge that you have read this Policy and agree to all its terms and conditions. By using the Website or its Services you agree to be bound by this Policy. If you do not agree to abide by the terms of this Policy, you are not authorized to use or access the Website and its Services.  
Contacting us  
If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us.  
This document was last updated on February 08, 2016
